https://www.womensnetwork.com.au/legal-privacy-statements/

Conditions
Women’s Network Australia Pty Ptd (WNA) reserves the right to refuse to write, edit or distribute any material that is or may be considered to be defamatory or misleading in any way.
WNA reserves the right to commence work only once payment is secured.
By engaging the services of WNA, you agree to indemnify WNA against any loss or liability whatsoever or howsoever arising out of any breach of copyright or intellectual property in the material to be edited, written or distributed, or any, defamatory or misleading statements or material contained therein.
WNA – Does not distribute adult related or questionable material.
WNA – Reserves the right to withhold the distribution of an advertisement for any reason.
Disclaimers
WNA – Retains the right to delete any or all information maintained on its web site.
WNA – Provides no warranties or guarantees regarding the accuracy or validity of any information supplied by third parties and contained in our website or distributed through our eNoticeBoard Service.
In no circumstances shall WNA be liable for any direct, incidental or consequential damages, lost profits, lost advertising or any indirect damages as a result of the use of our services.
All links and references to outside organisations (excluding WNA) are implicitly independent of WNA. WNA does not endorse, approve, certify, or control these external references and does not guarantee or assume responsibility for their accuracy.
Editorial content and graphics on this site are protected by copyright and may not be copied without the permission of WNA.
In no event shall WNA be liable to any parties for any delays, inaccuracies, errors or omissions with respect to the use of our services; including editing, writing, distribution and recommendations.
By visiting and using this site, the user accepts all risks and responsibility for loss, damage, costs and other consequences resulting from using this website and any websites linked to it.
In the event that litigation arises only Australian courts will have jurisdiction for claims against WNA.
Use of our Brand
Women’s Network Australia (WNA) Members have permission to use their Member eBadge logotype as a link to WNA’s website. In addition, the image can be displayed on their corporate stationery and approved promotional materials. However, the names and/or logos of WNA may not be used for the promotion of personal businesses or endeavours.
WNA partners, sponsors and the general public must obtain written permission from WNA to use the name(s) and/or likenesses or logos of WNA, WNA Community Partnership Project or Working Women Magazine.
WNA reserve the right to request the removal of a link to the www.womensnetwork.com.au website, or to take appropriate legal action in the event that a link is defamatory or otherwise harmful to WNA, or our Members.
Although WNA’s website includes links providing direct access to other Internet sites, WNA takes no responsibility for the content or information contained on those other sites and does not exert any editorial or other control over those other sites.
WNA welcomes links to our site. Other organisations and individuals may freely link to the www.womensnetwork.com.au provided that such links are not defamatory or otherwise harmful to WNA, our Members or the general public. WNA requests that any outside organisation or individual providing a link informs WNA of the link by E: admin@womensnetwork.com.au. ©
Privacy Statement
Women’s Network Australia Pty Ltd recognises that your privacy is very important to you and we are committed to promoting confidence in the manner in which your personal information is handled by us.
Women’s Network Australia Pty Ltd is bound by, and committed to, supporting the Australian Privacy Principles (APP) which were enacted in March 2014.
The following statement explains how Women’s Network Australia collects, uses, discloses and protects this information on its web site. Specifically the:
Collection – personal information is only collected to ensure Members and prospective Members are able to be contacted and made aware of services available.
Use and Disclosure – information will only be used for the benefit of the membership, principally to contact Members, and no information will be disclosed to any third party without prior approval.
Data Quality – we will ensure any data collected will be accurate, complete and current.
Data Security – we will protect data from misuse, loss or unauthorised use.
Openness – the type of information collected is openly available to anyone.
Identifiers – no Commonwealth or State identifiers are collected or used.
Anonymity – it is impracticable for Members to remain anonymous.
Transborder Data Flows – no information will be transferred overseas without prior approval.
Sensitive Information – sensitive information is not collected.
Access and Correction – we encourage personal information to be regularly updated and personal information collected to be available to the individual concerned.
Resolving Problems Related To Your Privacy
If you need to make a complaint about your private information or about a possible privacy breach regarding access to your personal information, please contact us on 1800 052 476 or write to us at:
Women’s Network Australia Pty Ltd
PO Box 5620, Manly QLD 4179.
We have an internal process to address such issues. The Office of Australian Information Commissioner (OAIC) suggests you allow 30 days for Women’s Network Australia Pty Ltd to respond to your privacy complaint, and then you may complain to the OAIC.
If you are not satisfied with our decision you can direct your complaint to the OAIC online via “Privacy Complaint Form” at www.oaic.gov.au.
Subscribe
Subscribe to the fortnightly WNA eNewsletter for business events, tips and information.
© Copyright 2020 Women's Network Australia.
All Rights Reserved.
Site by Thirteen Digital.
